# Ada Mandala

# **Consultant Software Engineer**

# 785-424-0182 ♣ ada.mandala@pm.me ☑ Lawrence, KS 66049 ♀

<u>/in/ada-mandala</u> 🛅

@ada-x64 Compared cubething.dev/about ##

# **Professional Summary**

Passionate software developer with a strong interest in systems-level programming and 5 years of experience. I am hoping to continue working with Rust, C++, Typescript, and Linux. Primarily experienced with game engine development and frontend web development. Frequently praised as diligent and insightful by peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals. I hope to use my interest in theoretical foundations and my practical insight to fulfill the engineering role at your company.

#### **Relevant Skills**

Rust

Typescript

WebAssembly

Azure DevOps

Git

Agile

# Experience

# Software Engineer

Prospective | Jun 2023 - Present

- Lead development on open-source frontend for a complex data visualization platform
- Collaborated closely with peers on a WASM-based, realtime database

# Software Engineer

Valorem Reply | Jun 2022 - May 2023

- Worked with a Fortune 100 company to bring their streaming service to a AAA gaming platform.
- Developed automation and process improvement, hosting the team scripts repository
- Lead department training exercise within 5 months of employment.

# Front-End Web Developer

Roll20 | Oct 2019 - Aug 2021

- Brought static design documents to life for the Roll20 Virtual Desktop.
- Integrated interactive user experiences for the original game Burn Bryte.
- Designed and developed local dev environment tool Mimic.

## Freelance Developer

Freelance | Jun 2018 - Jun 2022

- Designed, developed, and integrated full-stack solutions to meet client needs
- Worked with clients on various platforms and in various industries including web, mobile, and desktop applications.

#### Education

Widther

Mathematics and Philosophy, BA, Honors

University of Kansas | 2017

#### **Relevant Courses**

Theory of Computation Graph Theory

## **Awards and Honors**

Paretsky Award for Creativity

Morse Scholarship for Excellence in Philosophy